(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョジョ…｡
Jojo...
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
き… 貴様がジョジョか…｡
Are you Jojo?
Well, Jojo, listen up!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
いいか ジョジョ よく聞け！➡
その 柱の男 サンタナは➡
The man born from the Pillar, Santana...
我々 人間を
石仮面で 吸血鬼にし➡
...uses the stone mask on humans...
パワーを上げてから
食料とするらしい｡
...to grant us incredible power
at the cost of being devoured like livestock!
危険すぎる！
サンタナを殺さねばならない！
He's extremely dangerous, so we must kill him!
Be careful, Jojo!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
気を付けろ ジョジョ！
Touch!
(ｼﾞｮｾﾌ)タッチー！
Hey... you were talking just earlier, right?
お前
さっき 言葉しゃべってたよなあ｡
ハロー！ ご機嫌いかが～？
Hello! How are you today?
ハッピー
うれピー よろぴくね～！
Happy, peppy, hellopy!
ハッピー
うれピー よろぴくね～！
サンタナさん さあ ご一緒に！
Mr. Santana, all together now!
３… ４…｡
Three, four!
Happy, peppy, hellopy!
ハッピー
うれピー よろぴくね～！
♬(ｵｰﾌﾟﾆﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
♬ 静寂の底から
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Timing:
Fadeout4
♬ 目覚めるその柱たち 時を越え
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
♬ 深紅の血潮が
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
Mazrim
Quality Check:
♬ 立ち上がる勇気を
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
♬ 惹きあわせる
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
♬ 受け継ぐ愛を 宿命と呼ぶなら
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
♬ 微笑む目で 次の手を
♬ 闇を欺いて
刹那を躱して
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
♬ 刃すり抜け奴らの間隙を突け
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
♬ つらぬいた信念が 未来を拓く
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
♬ Like a Bloody Storm
熱くLike a Bloody Stone
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
♬ 血脈に
刻まれた因縁に
Distro:
ExWizzard
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
♬ 浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆
Nigirishimete
So hold them close.
♬ 握りしめて
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 13: "Jojo Versus The Ultimate Life Form"
Happy, peppy, hellopy!
ハッピー
うれピー よろぴくね～！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
貴様 ジョジョ ふざけてるのか！
Dammit Jojo, is this a joke to you?!
Jojo... what are you doing?!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ジョジョ お前 何しとるんじゃ…｡
Oh, I was just wondering what kind of a guy he was,
so I needed to see for myself.
いや～ ひょっとすると こいつ➡
いいやつなのかもしれねえ
と思ってさ｡
探りを入れてんのよ！
It wouldn't be fair to assume he's a bad guy, right?
悪者と 最初から考えんのは
よくねえと思うの 俺｡
バカ言うな！ 俺の部下が
こんなに 殺されたんだぞ！
Don't be stupid!
Look at how many of my men he killed!
Shut it! You people got what was coming to you!
うるせえ！ そいつは
てめえらの自業自得よ！
You made him your guinea pig
and shot him with a machine gun, dumbass!
実験したり
ﾏｼﾝｶﾞﾝ ぶっ放したりすっからだ！
パープリン！
Besides, that's not why I'm here.
それに 俺はだな｡
Speedwagon, I'm here to take you back to New York!
スピードワゴン あんたを
ニューヨークへ 連れ帰るために➡
ここへ来たんだぜ！
I have no part in this fight!
こいつとケンカする 理由はない！
Now, where were we? Happy, peppy, hellopy!
さあ ご一緒に！
ハッピー
うれピー よろぴくね～！
おおっ！
What's that, you're just gonna ignore me?
何だ？ こいつ｡
まるっきり 俺を無視しやがって｡
Now I'm a little pissed off.
ちょっと ムッときたね～｡
Fine, I'll just send him on a little trip!
《よし！ 足を引っ掛けて
転ばしてやるぜ！》
なっ！
ううっ…
ど… どうなったんだ!?
W-What was that?!
い… 今の感触は一体!?
This weird feeling... it hurts!
(ｻﾝﾀﾅ)初めて… 見る…｡
First time... seeing...
What is... this tool?
何だ… この… 道具…｡
He spoke! He does have intelligence!
しゃべった！
やはり 理解している！
He was somehow able to completely master our language!
我々の言葉を どうやったのか
完全に マスターしている！
す… すげえ！
A-Amazing!
He was able to take the gun apart
so quickly and precisely, like a machine!
時計みたいに 滑らかで➡
正確な動作で
銃を分解しちまった！
あれを覚えるのに 何時間かの
訓練が必要だというのに！
It normally takes hours of practice to do something like that!
Th-That means he's more intelligent than we suspected!
す… すごい 知能の持ち主
ということか｡
So bright... I have never seen lights like this.
(ｻﾝﾀﾅ)まぶしい！➡
こんな光も
初めて お目にかかる…｡
He wasn't the one under observation...
観察していたのは
わしらの方ではない！➡
やつの方だった！
It was us!
Hey, fella!
おい こら！
If you get what I'm saying, then give me some answers!
言葉が分かんなら
返事ぐらいしろよなあ｡
Knock knock?
ノック ノック｡
なっ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)危ない！ ジョジョ！
Watch out, Jojo!
うっとおしいぞ…
この 原始人が…｡
You are... irritating me... you primitive fool.
うお～！ 何だ!?
What the-?!
Maximum Length
Maximum Pressure
Rib Blades (Alternate Name: Open Ribs)
Rib Blades
(Alternate Name: Open Ribs)
Each individual rib can rotate and extend in any direction!
Each rib can rotate and extend
in any direction
Jojo!
ジョジョ～！
ぐああっ！
ぐあっ！
火花… 何だ？ この人間は｡➡
Spar... ks?
What kind... of human... is this?
I could not absorb him... into my body...
俺の体に…
吸収されず はじき飛んだ…｡
He flew away...
The leg... that grazed me... is fine...
さっき…
触れた足も… 無事のようだ…｡
I have never seen... someone like this... before...
こんな人間は 初めて 出会う…➡
This man... is he an extraordinary specimen?
あの男だけ 特別なのか…➡
Or could it be... that all of humanity... has become like this?
それとも この時代の人間…➡
全員 そうなのか…｡
うっ… うう…｡
うあ～！
うむ やはり
あの男だけ 特別のようだ…｡
I see... this man really is something... special.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
うう～！ ジョジョ 恐ろしい…｡
Jojo, this is terrifying!
あ… あ… ああ…｡
Uncle...
じいさん…｡
You son-of-a-bitch!
野郎！ じいさんを放しやがれ！
Get your filthy hands off my uncle!
Now I'm ready to pummel you!
戦いたくなったぜ！
てめえを 博物館に飾ってやる！
They'll show you in a museum once I'm through with you!
It seems that humans... have evolved... just a bit...
人間も… 少しは進化したのか…｡
おおおおおお！ てめえ！
Why you-!
波紋を ぶん流してやる！
I'm gonna blast my Ripple right through you!
くっ！ は… 波紋で床の血が！
Th-The blood on the floor is being affected by the Ripple?!
波紋が効かねえ！
The Ripple isn't working!
It's bouncing off of Santana and onto the floor,
making the Ripple act like drops of water hitting a raincoat!
レインコートの表面を
雨が 流れ落ちるように➡
波紋が サンタナの体から地面へ
流れ落ちて 血に反応している！
His skin is just like the scarf Straits was wearing...
It's acting like a conductor!
こいつの皮膚は ストレイツォの
マフラーと同じように➡
アースになっているんだ！
やはり…
こいつの体と 俺は反発し合う｡
I was right, his body is somehow able to reject mine.
おおおおああああ！
ああ～！ お… 俺の拳が！
M-My fist!
うう…｡
ああっ！ ああ…｡
It's fine!
ある！
ああ…｡
W-Well how about that?
な… なあ～んちゃって…｡
Good thing I pulled my fist back at the last second...
一瞬早く 手首を
内側に丸めたので 助かったぜ！
But goddamn, the Ripple isn't working on him...
だが なんてこった！
こいつには 波紋が効かねえ！
どうすりゃいいんだ…｡
Now what should I do?!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)いや！ 違う！➡
No, you're wrong!
効果はある！
波紋が ガードしているのだ！
It really did work!
The Ripple was protecting you!
ジョジョは あの 恐ろしい肉体に
食われずに済む｡
It's the only reason you weren't absorbed into his dreadful body!
Don't be so brash!
バカ言え！
フグを食うとき どうするか…｡
What does a chef do before he prepares pufferfish?
殺してから 毒の部分を取り除いて
食べればいい！
He removes the poisonous parts so it will be safe to eat!
And that's exactly how Santana sees the Ripple!
サンタナにとって 波紋は
ただ それだけのことにすぎない！
くそ～！ とんでもねえぜ！
何か 方法を考えなきゃあな｡
Damn it, this is such a mess!
I need to think of something fast!
せめて
無事 逃げ出す方法だけでもよ！
Something to get out of here alive, at least!
駄目だ！ 絶対に
そいつを 外に出してはならん！
Impossible!
You cannot allow this beast to get outside, or mankind is doomed!
人類の危機なのだ！
うるせえ！
Shut it! Don't act like this wasn't
your fault in the first place, you dumbass!
自分のしたこと 忘れて➡
勝手な せりふ
言うんじゃねえ このアホ！
Can't you see I'm already under enough pressure?
その上 俺に
プレッシャーまで かける気か!?
おっ！
おりゃ～！
ナイフを 突き刺して➡
I'll stab him with this knife, then send the Ripple directly into his body!
体内に 波紋を送り込んでやる！
うう！
He made his body act like rubber to stop the knife!
《ゴムみたいに
体に包み込みやがった！》
だが これは どう かわす！
But will you be able to avoid this?
皮膚が駄目なら
目ん玉に波紋だぜ！
If not your skin, I'll just blast the Ripple right into your eye!
It's the perfect plan!
完璧だよ この作戦は！
にゃ… にゃに～!?
W-Whyat?!
Even his eyes are like rubber!
目ん玉まで ゴムのようだ！
まずい！ ジョジョ 逃げろ～！
It's dangerous! Jojo, get away!
なっ！
ぐああっ！
ジョジョ～！
Jojo!
あの位置への攻撃は
しばらく 呼吸ができん！
A blow like that to the midsection would have knocked the breath out of him!
ふ～む｡
Breathing?
呼吸か 血液で生じる
エネルギーらしいな…｡
A type of energy... traveling with the flow of blood.
But... now...
しかし… 気絶していては
ただの 人間にすぎないな…｡
Unconscious, you're nothing more than a regular human.
Jojo, you have to breathe to create a Ripple!
ジョジョ～！
波紋の呼吸をしろ～！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)うわぁ～！
呼吸をするんだ！
ああっ！➡
Just breathe!
Control the Ripple with your breathing, Jojo!
波紋の呼吸をしてくれ～！
ジョジョ～！
も… もう駄目だ！
こうなったら 自爆スイッチを！
I-It's no good! I'll have to throw the self-destruct switch!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
はぁ… はぁ… はぁ…｡
For the Fatherland...
我が祖国よ…｡➡
For glory!
永遠なれ！
Hold on, Stroheim!
待て！ シュトロハイム！
あっ！
No need to panic!
慌てるんじゃあねえぜ｡
I had to take a gamble!
山を掛けたんだぜ！
表から駄目なら 内部からだ！
Since attacking from the outside didn't work,
I decided to try attacking with the Ripple from the inside!
食うときなら
じかに 波紋を流せると思ってな！
Jojo!
ジョジョ～！
This is exactly what I was waiting for. The perfect plan!
この 取り込むときを
待っていたのよ！ 完璧だぜ！
Eat Ripple!
食らえ 波紋！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ･ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)おお～！
ぐっ…｡
はぁ… はぁ… はぁ…｡
り… 理解したぜ｡
I think I get it now...
While I was in that freak's body,
I figured out how he's absorbing people!
こいつの ぞ～っとするような
体内に入って➡
消化吸収の秘密を 理解したぜ！
Every one of his cells produces digestive fluid,
allowing him to ingest people on a cellular level!
この化け物は 細胞の一つ一つから
消化液を出して➡
相手の細胞を 食っていく！
だから 体に取り込めるし
一体化してるように見えるんだ！
That's how he pulls people inside of him,
making it appear as if they've been absorbed!
I just barely deflected his digestive fluids
with the Ripple at the last second!
俺は その 消化液に
食われる瞬間➡
波紋を送り込んだから
助かったんだ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
だが！ ジョジョの波紋は弱い！
But your Ripple is still weak, Jojo!
It wasn't enough to kill him!
やつを
殺すほどのものではなかった！
So you're trying to pull yourself back together, huh?!
また 肉片がくっついて
元に戻ろうってんだろ！
Thanks to my battle with Straits,
I have a pretty good idea how you freaks operate!
ストレイツォとの戦いで
経験済みだから➡
お前の行動は
計算の内に入ってんのよ！
Stroheim!
シュトロハイム！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)あっ… ああ…｡
イテッ！
てめえ 聞いてんのか！
Pay attention, damn you!
こいつも 太陽に弱いのか？
Is he affected by the sun?!
Y-Yes!
あ… ああ！ ジョースター！
Joestar, the carvings in the cave indicated that Santana is weakened by the sun!
洞窟壁画の文字に 書いてある！
サンタナは 太陽に弱い｡
やつは 太陽を克服するために➡
That's part of the reason why he created the stone mask!
石仮面を作ったのだからな！
くっ…｡
ぐっ…｡
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
何をしている!? ジョースター！➡
What the hell are you doing, Joestar?!
That door leads right outside!
外へ通じる扉を 開けるなんて！
Why you, I'm gonna roast your arm in the sun!
てめえ 太陽の光で
やっつけてやるぜ！
くっ… うう…｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
あんなに 息せき切って➡
He's running out of breath...
It's preventing him from using the Ripple!
波紋の呼吸が乱れている！
訓練された波紋ではないから
戦いに疲労している！
He never trained to use the Ripple in battle, and it's wearing him out!
いいかげんにするんだな｡
この 原始人が！
I've had enough of this... you filthy primitive!
おりゃあ！
ああっ！
Jojo, the Ripple comes from your breathing!
ジョジョ～！
波紋の呼吸をしろ～！
呼吸をしろったって
疲れてんだよ！ ちくしょう！
How the hell am I supposed to breathe when I'm this tired?!
Goddamn it!
Now I'm pissed off!
もう 俺は頭にきたぞ！
No matter what happens, I'm climbing up these stairs
to give this bastard a taste of the sun!
何が何でも この階段を上って➡
この野郎に
日光浴をさせてやる！
な… 何だ!?
W-What the-?!
重いぞ！ か… 体が重い…｡
I feel heavy... so heavy!
What the hell is this?!
な… 何だ？ これは！
Meat Invaders
Meat Invaders (Alternate Name: The Ferocious Flesh)
(Alternate Name: The Ferocious Flesh)
Santana's flesh?!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)サンタナの肉片が！
ううっ！ す… 吸い取られる！
I-It's eating me!
こ… この野郎！
Y-You bastard...
くっ… 前に！
I have to move...
I never could have imagined a human like you
would be born during my slumber.
(ｻﾝﾀﾅ)俺が 眠っている間に➡
こんな人間が
生まれていたとはな…｡
うぬぬぬ…｡
ああっ！
ぬぬぬぬぬ～…｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)おおっ！
Please allow the great Stroheim to lend you a hand!
後は せめて➡
この シュトロハイムに
任せてもらうぞ！
If opening this door is all that can be done,
then it's the very least I can do.
この扉を 開ければいいんだな｡
それぐらいなら
俺にも できることよ！
Y-You... Stroheim!
お… お前 シュトロハイム｡
ふん！ この げすどもが！
You pathetic creature.
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)うおっ！ ああ～！
I was so close!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)あと 数cmのところで…｡
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)ぐうう～！
Resistance is futile.
(ｻﾝﾀﾅ)
《無駄なあがきよ｡ ふん！》
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)くっ… くぁぁぁぁ～！
《くっ！ ヤバいぜ…》
This isn't good...
Hey, Joestar! Can I ask you something?
おい ジョースター！
１つ 頼まれてくれるか？
What, dammit?!
何だ!? ちくしょう！
今 どうするか 考えてんだ！
I'm trying to figure out what to do, so shut up!
黙ってろ！
聞け～っ！
Listen!
Do you see that axe on the wall?
そこの壁に
おのが飾ってあるだろう！➡
If you can reach it, use it to cut off my leg!
届くか？
それで 俺の足を断て！
W-What?!
な… 何!?
俺の足を切断しろ！
そうすれば あの扉に手が届く！
Just cut my leg off, and then I can reach the door!
お… お前…｡
You... You really expect me to do something that brutal?!
俺に そんな 残酷なこと
やれってのか!?
早くしろ！
やつの肉体が 戻っていくぞ！
Hurry up!
He's already pulling himself together!
うるせえ！ 医者でもねえ俺に
そんなこと 頼むな！
Shut it!
Only a doctor should do stuff like that!
俺は これでも
誇り高き ドイツ軍人！
I am a proud officer of the German army!
その程度の 覚悟はできて
この任務に 就いておるのだ！
I was prepared to make sacrifices when I took this assignment!
祖国のためなら 足の２本や３本
簡単にくれてやるわ！➡
I would gladly sacrifice two, even three limbs
for the glory of the Fatherland!
So hurry up, Joestar!
早くしろ！ ジョースター！
やかましい！
Knock it off already!
そんなに 切ってほしけりゃ
切ってやるぜ！
You want me to cut it off, then I'll do it!
Hurry up and cut it already!
ああ！ 切ってほしいのだ～！
《くっそ～！
腰抜けかと思っていたが➡
Damn! I thought he was a coward,
but he has some real grit when it comes down to it!
こいつ 土壇場では
底力のある男だぜ！➡
We may think differently, but I have to respect you, Stroheim!
考え方は違えど 敬意を表すぜ！
シュトロハイム！》
I'm sorry!
すまねえ！ ウォー！
ぐっ…｡
ウォォォォォォーッ！
NUUUUU！
NUUUAHHHHH…｡
How do you like that? Now you're bathing in sunlight!
ざまあみろ！
太陽を浴びさせたぜ！
AH～！
Did we do it?
やったか…｡
W-What the-?!
な… 何!?
うお～っ！
He's getting inside my body through the wound in my leg!
俺の足の傷口から 体内に～！
You bastard!
この野郎！
うぁぁぁ～！
な… なんてこった！
What is this?!
He went into Stroheim because he can't use the Ripple!
波紋の使えぬ
シュトロハイムの方に行くとは！
あっ！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)お… お… おお…｡➡
お… 俺の体内にサンタナが！
Santana is crawling around inside me!
な… なんて生き物だ！
なんという生への執着！
W-What an amazing creature!
What a tenacious will to live!
If he's inside Stroheim, then he can survive being out in the sun!
シュトロハイムの体内なら
太陽の下でも やつは生きれる｡
This is horrifying...
お… 恐ろしい！ 俺は恐ろしい！
Do you know what the most horrifying part about this is, Joestar?
何が恐ろしいかって
ジョースター！➡
My leg isn't hurting anymore...
足の傷口が 痛くないんだ｡
快感に変わっているんだぜ～！
It's beginning to feel absolutely wonderful!
Wha-
なっ！
おお…｡
Stroheim!
シュトロハイム！
ううっ…｡
くっ… ぐっ！
なっ！ 貴様！
You...
No way...
ま… まさか!?
Joestar!
ジョースター！
You're witnessing the power of the ultimate life form, Santana!
今まで見たのが
究極の生物サンタナだ！
There's no saving me now...
こうなったら
俺は もう助からん…｡
自分ごと
こいつを吹っ飛ばす 覚悟よ！
I'll sacrifice myself to put an end to this creature!
But there's something I must tell you before I die...
しかし 死ぬ前に お前に
言っておきたいことがある！➡
As much as it pains me, you need to know, Englishman!
いまいましいが
イギリス人のお前にな！
我が ドイツ軍は
単なる 軍事上の好奇心で➡
The glorious German army did not simply
awaken Santana for military use!
サンタナを 目覚めさせたのでは
ないということを！
何!? こんなときに
いきなり 何を言い出す！
What... What are you going on about?!
聞け！ いや お前は
聞かなければならん宿命にある！
Listen!
You were destined to hear what I have to say!
Our army recently discovered that
other Pillar Men exist besides Santana!
現在 我が軍は
サンタナの他に➡
柱の男を ヨーロッパの…➡
They're located somewhere in Europe!
ある場所の地下から
発見している！
グォォァァ！
な… 何だと!?
W-What are you saying?!
Stroheim, what are you talking about?!
シュトロハイム
何を言ってるんだ～！
I'm trying to tell you that Santana isn't the only one!
つまり サンタナは
１人ではないということだ！
We've been unraveling the mystery behind these creatures
that have lain dormant here for the last two thousand years!
我々 ドイツ軍は
2,000年周期で 眠りにつく➡
柱の男という生命体の
驚異的な能力の 謎を追ってきた！
近い将来 やつらは目覚める！
But soon they will rise! And if we don't find
a weakness besides sunlight, mankind will be doomed!
やつらの 太陽以外の弱点を
つかまぬかぎり 人類は滅びる！➡
We were experimenting on him so we could learn his weakness!
だから 我が軍は こいつを 実験し
調査する必要があったのだ！➡
After what happened fifty years ago, it is your destiny to fight them!
貴様は 50年前からの因縁で➡
やつらと 戦わねばならない
運命にある！
Joestar, your Ripple is still far too weak!
ジョースター！ 貴様の波紋は
弱すぎて やつらを倒せん！
Head to Rome, for there is someone you must meet there!
ローマへ行け！
ローマに行って
ある人物に 会うのだ！➡
It is someone Speedwagon knows quite well!
それは スピードワゴンの
よく知っている人物！
オゴォォォー！
Y-You're trying to control my body so you can hide in that well...
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)こ… こいつ
井戸の中へ 逃げ込もうと➡
俺の体を 操っている！
...but I'll blow myself up before that
and expose you to the sun, Santana!
だが すぐに 体を開けて➡
太陽を拝ませてやるぜ サンタナ！
Stroheim... you...
シュトロハイム 貴様…｡
フフフ… 人間の偉大さは
恐怖に耐える 誇り高き姿にある｡
"Courage consists not in hazarding without fear,
but being resolutely minded in a just cause..."
ギリシャの歴史家
プルタルコスの言葉だ｡
The words of the Greek historian, Plutarchus.
さらばだ…
いまいましい イギリス野郎…｡
Goodbye, you irritating British bastard!
やめろ！
話は まだ半分だぜ～！
Wait, we aren't done talking yet!
(爆発音)
ぐあ～っ！
Dammit, you stubborn soldier!
ちくしょう…
この へっぽこ軍人め！
カッコつけやがって…｡
Making such a spectacle of your death...
あっ！
はあっ！
Santana!
サンタナ～！
どけい！
どかずば 死ぬのみだ ジョジョ！
Move!
Move it or die, Jojo!
I have to steady my breathing... to control the Ripple!
《呼吸を整えろ！
波紋の呼吸を！》
HUOHAHHHHHHHHH！
COOOOOOOO！
ぐわ～！
どけい！ お前は 最初から
負け犬ムードだったのだ！
Move! You were setting yourself up
to lose the moment you fought me!
Y-You're just about to say,
"Haven't you learned your lesson, you insolent primitive?!"
て… てめえの次に吐く
せりふは➡
｢思い知ったか
この 原始人が｣だ！
Haven't you learned your lesson, you insolent primitive?!
思い知ったか！
この 原始人が！➡
はっ！
UOOHHHHHHHH！
It's high noon!
今は ちょうど 真昼時！
You're just like ham and eggs being cooked
on both sides from the sun and its reflection!
頭上からの光と
水面からの反射で➡
両面焼きのハムエッグよ！
You should have thought about the sun's
position in the sky before jumping in the well, you idiot!
地球の自転による
太陽の移動のことを 考えて➡
井戸に飛び込め！ スカタン！
And I won't let you get under the water, either!
水面下までは
落下させねえんだよ！
ウォ～！
GYAHHAAAA！
ふぅ…｡
《た… 太陽のおかげで
助かった！》
I was saved by the sun...
...and it turned him completely to stone!
《こいつを
完全に 石にしてやったぜ！》
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
♬ I'll be the roundabout
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
I'll spend the day your way
♬ I spend the day away
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬～
The music dance and sing
♬ The music dance and sing
They make the children really ring
♬ They make
the children really ring
♬ Spend the day away
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
In and around the lake
♬ In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
and they stand there
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
♬ I'll be there with you
There with you
Next Episode
The tragedy that befell my grandfather!
You couldn't even beat a pigeon!
Keep that ultraviolet light on them!
Awaken, my masters!
Episode 14:
"The Ultimate Warriors of an Ancient Age"
(ｼｰｻﾞｰ)
俺の祖父に起こった 悲劇は！
ならば てめえは
このハトにさえ 勝てやしねえぜ！
(幹部)紫外線の照射量を
もっと 多くしろ！
(ﾜﾑｳ)目覚めたまえ！
我が あるじたちよ！